HENRIQUE MELO

SKILLS

- Frontend
- HTML CSS JavaScript
- Backend
- PHP · MySQL ·
- WordPress Codex and APIs
- Theme Development
- Divi Astra Avada
- Plugin Development
- Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) •
- Toolset Types
- Form Development
- Contact Form 7 · Gravity Forms ·
- WPForms
- eCommerce Development
- WooCommerce · WP eCommerce ·
- BigCommerce for WordPress

WordPress Expert | CMS Development

RESUME PROFILE

Hi, I am Henrique, a Senior WordPress developer with over 14 years of experience. I developed a wide range of WordPress websites. These websites include general sites, business sites, and eCommerce sites with woo-commerce experience. I customize many WordPress themes using builders like Divi and Elementor.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Wordpress Developer	2022 - Present
Self Employed	Brazil
Senior WordPress Developer	02/2020 - 06/2022
Aktie Now	Brazil
Wordpress Developer DBSP	04/2017 - 06/2020 Brazil
WordPress Developer	2014 - 2017
Calina Marketing Digital	Brazil
WordPress Developer CMA CGM	2011 - 2014 Brazil
Wordpress Developer	2008 - 2011
Sciensa	Brazil
Wordpress Developer Certification WP Academy	2018

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer	2004 - 2008
Engineering	
Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte	

Powered by Shancu